oh look at the lotion he got some
in his hair it's coming out of the
glasses you got a white dream dripping
down he's got this stuff tom cruise uses
[Music]
hey guys welcome to the show my guests
today really need no introduction
they're global superstars they've
probably worked out three times already
today each it's mark wahlberg and kevin
hart stars of me time hi guys sir hi how
you doing josh i'm doing well except i'm
a little bit worried because i literally
have nothing prepared today and i've
been told that you guys have done the
prep today that's false
yeah that's right that's right good job
it's just a little taste of what you're
gonna get all right let's get you
stopped
it's not being a pansy so what do i need
to know what are we doing here today all
right so look we're asking you questions
right we're gonna see how i know how
well you know me and how well you know
kevin kevin will ask you questions about
me
i'll ask you questions about kevin i
feel like i've been talking to you guys
for over a decade each we've talked
thousands of times i probably know
everything there is to know so i'm not
okay how many movies has the rock done
with kevin the rock has because there
are two jumanjis or central intelligence
there's the hobbs and shaw four wrong
wrong
what was the fit what was wrong yeah
yeah okay okay maybe just one each maybe
just i gotta get it i gotta get my aim
together okay you gotta take it okay one
more question you got one more than that
we're done when kevin does the movie
with the rock how many times does kevin
have to kiss rox tuckus
huh took us what does that mean that's
what the kids say it that's how they
called it
there's no real answer to that you don't
answer that
standing up all right the first concert
kevin ever attended was the michael
jackson concert true or false false
yeah you're right why would you think
that i wouldn't go see michael jackson
oh he's a great one
mike if i could have i couldn't afford
it sesame street on ice
all right that's enough
okay there you go mark wisconsin marcus
starred in five films directed by peter
berg uh that's false that's i feel like
they're full like we're all the same
movie that's true do you not know mark
wahlberg's filmography is it not enough
that you're trying to meet water guns
you don't have to yell at me long
survivor deep water horizon patriots day
mile 22 spencer confidential the answer
is true you're gonna
go combo no he's gonna combo all right
you're gonna oh look at the lotion he
got some in his hair it's coming
out of the glasses you got a white dream
dripping down he's got this stuff tom
cruise
kevin served as the emcee for whose
comedy central roast in 2015.
he's not going to get it right he's not
going to give up
you know what man you can't even help
you eddie murphy
wrong eddie murphy's rose i remember he
was because he's black
she can't rose eddie murphy eddie murphy
you think that i'm not going to tell him
what you just said insulting eddie
you got some nerve for what associated
me with eddie because we're both black
but you're both really probably again
good luck explaining that today to the
naacp
it's over for you after the day how many
acting credits does kevin have on his
imdb who don't you don't know that yeah
i do oh yeah what's the answer you don't
think i have the answer yeah give me a
gun no because kevin's hair color will
change everything
be greater than the in a
minute you spray that
oh my god you know the mess you'll make
right now
mark sprays his abs on there it is i'm
giving out body information oh this is a
good one how many nipples does mark have
josh knows this from experience yeah
he had to know three nipples that's
actually good
how do you know that jesus why do you
know he has yeah why is this the one
when i get right now we draw you off see
if you get it right we're fanning oh gee
thanks oh by the way that's more
annoying
because that's it to walk around with we
get
yeah when i die of pneumonia i want you
to speak at my funeral wow
okay god mark you give him the last one
you know there was an actor let's see if
you can guess this actor i was doing a
film yeah showed up to work late one day
was doing an audition we were doing a
very famous scene and me and the
director started giving him a hard time
because he was late he threw a
marshmallow at me i caught it i threw it
back it missed and hit him in the head
and he tried to fight me
for real that sounds like a classic
leonardo dicaprio
is it departed is it anyone from the
department alcohol
no you're not going to tell it though
you can't tell no i'll tell ya
uh josh i am disappointed because you
are what i would refer to as an almanac
when it comes to the world of film i've
never seen you miss the one that you got
right was about his nipples which had
nothing to do with movies at all
and nothing to do with me true
all right i'm gonna go to the sauna dry
off a little bit
um gentlemen congratulations on the film
i would say this has been fun but it
hasn't it has been fun josh it's always
good to see you man i think when you
watch it back you'll appreciate it i'm
never gonna look at this again
[Music]
you